You notice I let them wait to the left where there's no line versus in that line.
The children don't need that core memory.
You know, when the kids grow up, they're going to say,
Mom, remember we used to walk past that white van and they used to give us candy and sodas and burgers?
And the mother's going to remember like, oh, shit, we were homeless.
But the kid doesn't have that core memory because they got junk.
They got shit.
You know what I'm saying?
As every kid should be allowed to get from an ice cream truck.
This right here is Ms. Shirley Raines.
Now, Shirley Raines works down in Skid Row in Los Angeles with houseless folks in providing not only food,
not only beauty services, not only candy, as she's here talking about the kids,
but she also provides kindness and compassion and respect to a community that oftentimes is not given any of those things.
And we have the honor of having her today on Small Doses Podcast.
So if you have any questions that you would like to me, you would like for me to ask Ms. Shirley Raines,
the Ms. Shirley Raines, make sure you drop them in the comments right here, right now.